<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/page/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/page/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-07-17T15:13:28+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/page/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Eun-jin Shin</title><subtitle>Graduate student studying computational astrophysics and cosmology in Seoul National University.</subtitle><author><name>Eun-jin</name></author><entry><title type="html">Welcome!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/page/2020/07/16/home.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome!" /><published>2020-07-16T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2020-07-16T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/page/2020/07/16/home</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/page/2020/07/16/home.html">&lt;p&gt;Hi, I’m Eun-jin, a graduate student studying computational astrophysics and cosmology at &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.snu.ac.kr/&quot;&gt;Seoul National University&lt;/a&gt;. 
I study the galaxy formation and evolution using cosmological simulation codes with &lt;a href=&quot;https://enzo-project.org/&quot;&gt;ENZO&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tapir.caltech.edu/~phopkins/Site/GIZMO.html&quot;&gt;GIZMO&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://wwwmpa.mpa-garching.mpg.de/gadget/&quot;&gt;GADGET-2&lt;/a&gt;. 
My current research interests are the formation and evolution of star cluster and black hole via galaxy merger. 
I’m particularly interested in modeling of supernova and stellar feedback, and propagation of supernova remnants on inter- and circum- galactic medium. 
My supervisor is &lt;a href=&quot;https://physics.snu.ac.kr/cosmo/index/index.html&quot;&gt;Ji-hoon Kim&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;img src=&quot;http://127.0.0.1:4000/ejshin/images/myphoto.png&quot; alt=&quot;placeholder&quot; title=&quot;my photo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Eun-jin</name></author><summary type="html">Hi, I’m Eun-jin, a graduate student studying computational astrophysics and cosmology at Seoul National University. I study the galaxy formation and evolution using cosmological simulation codes with ENZO, GIZMO and GADGET-2. My current research interests are the formation and evolution of star cluster and black hole via galaxy merger. I’m particularly interested in modeling of supernova and stellar feedback, and propagation of supernova remnants on inter- and circum- galactic medium. My supervisor is Ji-hoon Kim.</summary></entry></feed>